# **Sarah Evans**

# Full Stack Web Developer

Phone 404-918-8152 LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarahgevans/

E-mail sarah.g.evans42@gmail.com Github https://github.com/n3m3sis42

Self-motivated full stack web developer with a passion for deep knowledge.

Experience in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript, React/Redux, Gatsby.js and GraphQL, with a background in functional MUMPS-based programming. Proven ability to master new technologies and solve difficult problems with strong skills in team-building and management. Once learned an unfamiliar coding language with only a binder of handwritten notes as a teaching tool!

### **Experience**

Dec 2017 - present Software Engineer

Policygenius, Inc - New York, NY

- + Build new features using Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, and GraphQL.
- + Troubleshoot and correct issues with production code.
- + Write and maintain automated tests using Rspec, Capybara, and Jest.

Iatric Systems - Boxford, MA

- + Provided advanced support for cloud-based and enterprise healthcare applications.
- + Resolved mission-critical issues with code, applications, and servers.
- + Participated in product design, development, testing, and support.

Apr 2005 - Dec 2011 Supervisor and Senior Developer

MEDITECH - Atlanta, GA

- + Managed a small team of support and development programmers.
- + Prioritized development tasks, ensuring my team met all deadlines.
- + Oversaw group code review process to ensure consistent quality of releases.
- + Developed custom software solutions and resolved escalated client issues.

## **Education**

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017 Flatiron School

Full Stack Web Development, immersive program

Sep 2003 - May 2006 Georgia State University

Undergraduate Coursework, Computer Science

Sep 1994 - May 1998 **Emory University** 

Bachelor of Arts, Psychology

#### **Skills**

JavaScript

Ruby on Rails

React/Redux

PostgreSQL/MS-SQL

GraphQL

HTML/CSS

**MUMPS**